<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-05T21:27:26-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Termoesu’s Fastpage</title><subtitle>Termoesu fastpage for Computer Science Principles.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Big Idea 5.4 Crowdsourcing</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/02/01/54Notes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Big Idea 5.4 Crowdsourcing" /><published>2023-02-01T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/02/01/54Notes</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have all experienced Crowdsourcing by using external data through API’s, namely RapidAPI. This data has influenced how we code and shown possibilities in obtaining and analyzing data. Discuss APIs you have used. I used a BasketballAPI for my last project with a bunch of data about basketball players Some other people used an API that gives you words for hangman Another person used an NBA API that gave random NBA players with their stats]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Big Idea 5.3 Computing Bias</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/02/01/53Notes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Big Idea 5.3 Computing Bias" /><published>2023-02-01T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/02/01/53Notes</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google “What age groups use Facebook” vs “… TikTok”? What does the data say? Is there purposeful exclusion in these platforms? Is it harmful? Should it be corrected? Is it good business? The older generation tend to use Facebook, while the new and young generation tend to use TikTok. 60% of the users on TikTok are ages 16-24. The average age of users that use Facebook range from 25 to 34 years old. These platforms do give purpose in giving information and entertainment to people, however it can be harmful as the content you receive can be very polarized, and usually put through algorithms to give the content you wish to see. It is definitely a good business, but takes advantage of people because many will believe whatever they see on social media, whether it is true or not. This makes our society less educated in certain topics and giving out information that is false to many others.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Project Blog</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/ProjectBlog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Blog" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/ProjectBlog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Portion of Project for CPT My portion of the project is going to be the search bar to find tips and tricks through articles and videos that help you along your fitness journey. Its is going to: have a search bar at top of the page have videos and articles embedded into the actual page allow users to search for certain articles or videos to help them with fitness Outline of materials required for CollegeBoard Row 1: Program Purpose and Function overall purpose of the program is so that users can find videos and articles that they want to watch or read so that they can receive guidance on their fitness journey The video will go over the functionality of the program, meaning how the search bar works and what happens when you click on videos or articles The input and output will be described in the video, so it will show the user inputting a certain article or video they want to watch, the output will provide user the list of articles or videos related to their search]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MCQ 2 Blog</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/MCQBlog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MCQ 2 Blog" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/MCQBlog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Score of MCQ #2]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Divide Reflection</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/digitaldivideblog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Divide Reflection" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/digitaldivideblog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Idea 5.2 Digital Divide Reflection What are the pros and cons on internet blockers at router and lack of admin password on lab machines at schools?]]></summary></entry></feed>