<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-31T00:56:43-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Termoesu’s Fastpage</title><subtitle>Termoesu fastpage for Computer Science Principles.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Project Blog</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/ProjectBlog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Blog" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/ProjectBlog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Portion of Project for CPT My portion of the project is going to be the search bar to find tips and tricks through articles and videos that help you along your fitness journey. Its is going to: have a search bar at top of the page have videos and articles embedded into the actual page allow users to search for certain articles or videos to help them with fitness Outline of materials required for CollegeBoard Row 1: Program Purpose and Function overall purpose of the program is so that users can find videos and articles that they want to watch or read so that they can receive guidance on their fitness journey The video will go over the functionality of the program, meaning how the search bar works and what happens when you click on videos or articles The input and output will be described in the video, so it will show the user inputting a certain article or video they want to watch, the output will provide user the list of articles or videos related to their search]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MCQ 2 Blog</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/MCQBlog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MCQ 2 Blog" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/30/MCQBlog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Score of MCQ #2]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Beneficial and Harmful Effects Blog Reflection</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/benefitharmblog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beneficial and Harmful Effects Blog Reflection" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/benefitharmblog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Idea 5.1 Beneficial and Harmful Effects Computing is the process of using computer technology to complete a given goal-oriented task. One benefit of computing is that it makes real life things much more accessible on the internet, such as electronic transactions. Another benefit is that computers make things easier for us, such as accessing information online through Google, and a lot of information can be given to pretty much anyone around the world. The last benefit is that communication has become easier because of computing. Now we are able to talk to anyone around the world through computers.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Divide Reflection</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/digitaldivideblog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Divide Reflection" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/digitaldivideblog</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Idea 5.2 Digital Divide Reflection What are the pros and cons on internet blockers at router and lack of admin password on lab machines at schools?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rebecca Presentation Notes</title><link href="https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/RebeccaNotes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rebecca Presentation Notes" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://dereksol.github.io/Tera/apcsp%20week%2020/2023/01/24/RebeccaNotes</id><author><name></name></author><category term="APCSP Week 20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notes she began by outlining the goal of their project explained the background of their initiative and the objectives they had for it she went over their front end after that discussed all of her existing features and how they can satisfy CRUD and College Board criteria what she still intend to incorporate into their project displayed a sample of one of their databases discussed the goals of their program, potential issues, and how their program would address those issues model, view, and control view explanation (How the API and Model Control Hacks are implemented in their project) outlined their hosting strategy for both the front and back ends of their projects displayed their scrum board and the planning they’ve done for how they’ll complete their project over time Finally, went over the team manifesto to conclude the presentation]]></summary></entry></feed>